const tasks = [
  {
    "type": "drag-platt-to-de",
    "question": "Gur Dai",
    "correct": ["Guten", "Tag"],
    "gloss": ["Guten", "Tag"]
  },
  {
    "type": "drag-platt-to-de",
    "question": "Hur gair't wat?",
    "correct": ["Wie", "geht's"],
    "gloss": ["wie", "geht", "es"]
  },
  {
    "type": "drag-platt-to-de",
    "question": "Fuul Dank",
    "correct": ["Vielen", "Dank"],
    "gloss": ["Vielen", "Dank"]
  },
  {
    "type": "drag-platt-to-de",
    "question": "Sünhair",
    "correct": ["Gesundheit"],
    "gloss": ["Gesundheit"]
  },
  {
    "type": "drag-platt-to-de",
    "question": "Jaa",
    "correct": ["Ja"],
    "gloss": ["Ja"]
  },
  {
    "type": "drag-platt-to-de",
    "question": "Naan",
    "correct": ["Nein"],
    "gloss": ["Nein"]
  },
  {
    "type": "drag-platt-to-de",
    "question": "Ik sen litj",
    "correct": ["Ich", "bin", "klein"],
    "gloss": ["Ich", "bin", "klein"]
  },
  {
    "type": "drag-platt-to-de",
    "question": "Dü best gurt",
    "correct": ["Du", "bist", "groß"],
    "gloss": ["Du", "bist", "groß"]
  },
  {
    "type": "drag-platt-to-de",
    "question": "Hi es net",
    "correct": ["Er", "ist", "nett"],
    "gloss": ["Er", "ist", "nett"]
  },
  {
    "type": "drag-platt-to-de",
    "question": "Gur Nacht",
    "correct": ["Gute", "Nacht"],
    "gloss": ["Gute", "Nacht"]
  }
];
